Guide to the Vassar College Drama Department Records, circa 1910-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series VI. Drama Department Production Material, circa 1910-2021
  - Production Files, circa 1910-2019
    - Blue Window, 1993 Nov 4 - 6 (Box 58)
    - The Danube, 1993 Nov 11 - 13 (Box 58)
    - Woyzeck, 1993 Nov 18 - 20 (Box 58)
    - The Merry Wives of Windsor, 1994 (Box 84)
    - Top Girls, 1994 Feb 24 - 26 (Box 84)
    - The Threepenny Opera, 1994 Apr 14 - 17 (Box 84)
    - Stage Blood, 1994 Apr 29 - 30 (Box 84)
    - All My Sons, 1994 May 6 - 7 (Box 84)
    - Waiting For Lefty, 1994 Oct 6 - 8 (Box 84)
    - A Shayna Maidel, 1994 Oct 27 - 29 (Box 84)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come, 1995 (Box 84)
    - The Lover, 1995 Oct 5 - 7; (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - A Seagull, 1995 (Box 84)
    - The Bald Soprano, 1995 Mar 2 - 4 (Box 84)
    - The Elektra Project, 1995 Apr 20 - 23 (Box 84)
    - The Balcony, 1995 Nov 10 - 11 (Box 84)
    - Bloody Poetry, 1995 Nov 17 - 18 (Box 84)
    - Wilder, Wilder, Wilder, 1996 Feb 22 - 24 (Box 84)
    - Thyestes, 1996 Mar 28 - 30; (3 folders) (Box 84)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, 1996 Apr 25 - 27 (Box 84)
    - Arms and the Man, 1996 Oct 10 - 12 (Box 84)
    - Salome, 1996 Nov 7 - 9 (Box 84)
    - The Cenci, 1996 Dec 5 - 7 (Box 84)
    - Quid Pro Quo, 1997 Mar 27, Apr 1 (Box 84)
    - John Gabriel Borkman, 1997 Apr 10 - 12; (3 folders) (Box 84)
    - Camille, 1997 Apr 24 - 26; (3 folders) (Box 84)
    - A Bright Room Called Day, 1997 Oct 9 - 12; (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - Falsettos, 1997 Nov 6 - 8; (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - The Great God Brown, 1997 Nov 20 - 22 (Box 85)
    - Eccentricities of a Nightingale, 1998 Feb 10 - 12; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - 4 Saints in 3 Act, 1998 Feb 26 - 28 (Box 85)
    - Circe, 1998 Apr 2 - 4 (Box 85)
    - Native Stone, 1998 Apr 16 - 18 (Box 85)
    - Parents Weekend, 1998 Apr 25 (Box 85)
    - Little Foxes, 1998 Oct 8 - 10 (Box 85)
    - The Conduct of Life, 1998 Oct 13 - 15 (Box 85)
    - Feigned Courtesans, 1998 Nov 19 - 21 (Box 85)
    - Two Workshop Production: Poof! And Desdemona, 1999 Feb 12 - 14 (Box 85)
    - The Merchant of Venice, 1999 Feb 24 - 27 (Box 85)
    - Antigona Furiosa, 1999 Apr 1 - 3; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - Our Country’s Good, 1999 Apr 15 - 17; (3 folders) (Box 85)
    - The Holy Highball, 1999 Apr 30 (Box 85)
    - Helen, 1999 Oct 7 - 9 (Box 85)
    - Phaedra, 1999 Nov 5 - 6 (Box 85)
    - Love of a Nightingale, 1999 Nov 17, 19; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - Mouthful of Birds, 1999 Nov 18, 20 (Box 85)
    - Nothing of Origins, The Directors Art, 1999 Dec 3; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - Orestes 2.0, 2000 Feb 24 - 26 (Box 85)
    - Electra, 2000 Mar 31 - Apr 1 (Box 85)
    - 2.5 Minute Ride, 2000 Apr 10 (Box 85)
    - The Fairy Queen: An Opera, 2000 Apr 13 - 15 (Box 85)
    - The Flies, 2000 Apr 26 - 29 (Box 85)
    - MSS Playwriting: Suffern and Paper Heart, 2000 Apr (Box 86)
    - As You Like It (Actors From London Stage), 2000 Sep 27 - 30 (Box 86)
    - Twelfth Night, 2000 Oct 26 - 28 (Box 86)
    - Hamlet, 2000 Nov 9 - 11 (Box 86)
    - Othello, 2000 Nov 17 - 18 (Box 86)
    - Ophelia, 2000 Dec 2 - 3 (Box 86)
    - Tempest, 2000 Dec 7 - 8 (Box 86)
    - Taming of the Shrew, 2001 Mar 1 - 3 (Box 86)
    - Avery Installation, 2001 Mar 30 - Apr 1 (Box 86)
    - Faust, 2001 Apr 12 - 14 (Box 86)
    - Henry IV Part 1, 2001 Apr 26 - 27 (Box 86)
    - Suitcase Productions, 2001 Oct - Nov (Box 86)
    - Waiting for Godot, 2001 Oct 10 - 12 (Box 86)
    - Love Chambers, 2001 Nov 2 - 4 (Box 86)
    - Chekov Project, 2001 Nov 8 - 9 (Box 86)
    - Avery Hall Documentary, 2001 Nov (Box 86)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 2001 Dec 6 - 8 (Box 86)
    - The Maids, 2001 Dec 6 - 9 (Box 86)
    - Tango Palace, 2002 Feb 14 - 17 (Box 86)
    - Angels in America, 2002 Mar 4 - 6 (Box 86)
    - The Rite of the Virtues and the seven deadly sins of the petty bourgeoisie, 2002 Apr 11 - 14 (Box 86)
    - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, 2002 May 2 - 3 (Box 86)
    - Rockaby and Footfalls, 2002 Oct 4 - 5 (Box 86)
    - FNU LNU, 2002 Oct 4 - 5 (Box 86)
    - SLAVS!, 2002 Oct 25 - 26 (Box 86)
    - The After Dinner Joke, 2002 Oct 31 - Nov 2 (Box 86)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 2002 Nov 5 - 9 (Box 86)
    - Cassandra, 2002 Nov 15 - 16 (Box 86)
    - Can't Stand Up for Falling Down, 2002 Nov 15 - 16 (Box 86)
    - Bar(re)s: a dance theater piece, 2002 Dec 4 - 7 (Box 86)
    - The Versailles Impromptu, 2003 Feb 26 - Mar 1 (Box 86)
    - Over Here, 2003 Mar 5 - 6 (Box 86)
    - The Hamlet Symphony, 2003 May 8 - 10 (Box 86)
    - Buried Child, 2003 Nov 4 - 8 (Box 86)
    - Spring Awakening, 2003 Nov 20 - 22 (Box 86)
    - Beijing Opera, 2003 Dec 7 (Box 86)
    - The Invention of Love, 2004 Feb 28 - Mar 3 (Box 86)
    - The Desire Project, 2004 Mar 1 - 3 (Box 86)
    - Cabaret, 2004 Apr 8 - 10 (Box 86)
    - The Secretaries, 2004 Apr 28 - 30 (Box 86)
    - Ol'Head Country Wisdom, 2004 May 12 (Box 86)
    - We Bombed in New Haven, 2004 Oct 11 - 14 (Box 86)
    - Aithra, 2004 Oct 11 - 14 (Box 86)
    - Las Meninas, 2004 Nov 18 - 20 (Box 86)
    - As You Like It, 2005 Feb 24 - 26 (Box 86)
    - Girls in Boys Pants, 2005 Feb 28 - Mar 2 (Box 86)
    - Fruit Cocktail, 2005 Mar 24 - 26 (Box 86)
    - Kate Crackernuts, 2005 Apr 6 - 9 (Box 86)
    - The Seagull, 2005 Apr 21 - 23 (Box 86)
    - Little Red Riding Hood, 2005 May 6 - 7 (Box 86)
    - Special Events - Entering in Verdant Skin, 2005 Fall (Box 87)
    - Entering in Verdant Skin, 2005 Sep 30 (Box 86)
    - The Illusion, 2005 Oct 11 - 14 (Box 86)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 2005 Nov 3 - 5 (Box 87)
    - Ensemble Project, 2005 Nov 17 - 19 (Box 87)
    - Uncle Vanya, 2005 Dec 1 - 3 (Box 87)
    - No Way to Treat a Lady, 2005 Dec 9 - 10 (Box 87)
    - SUS, 2006 Apr 20 - 22 (Box 87)
    - Lord Padraic O'Shaugnessy, 2006 Mar 7 - 10 (Box 87)
    - Live Feed, 2006 Apr 8 (Box 87)
    - Special Events, 2006 Spring (Box 87)
    - Treaty, 2006 May 4 - 5 (Box 87)
    - Pygmalion, 2007 Oct 10 - 12 (Box 87)
    - Inauguration, 2006 Oct 25 - 28 (Box 87)
    - OTMA, 2006 Oct 25 - 28 (Box 87)
    - Into the Woods, 2006 Nov 16 - 18 (Box 87)
    - Gallathea, 2007 Mar 1 - 3 (Box 87)
    - Quills, 2007 Apr 12 - 14 (Box 87)
    - Oedipus at Colonus, 2007 Apr 27 (Box 87)
    - Macbeth, 2007 Oct 4 - 6 (Box 87)
    - Cloud Nine, 2007 Nov 7 - 9 (Box 87)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 2007 Nov 29 - Dec 1 (Box 87)
    - Friday Afternoon Theater, 2008 May 7 - 10 (Box 87)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, 2008 Apr 24 - 26; (2 folders) (Box 87)
    - Dynamo Theatre Lab, 2008 Feb 22 - Apr 11 (Box 87)
    - Playwriting Competition, 2008 Spring (Box 87)
    - The Winters Tale, 2008 Sep 18 - 20 (Box 87)
    - Carlisle: A different three sisters, 2008 Sep (Box 87)
    - First Lady Suite, 2008 Nov 6 - 8; (2 folders) (Box 88)
    - Three Sisters, 2008 Nov 20 - 22; (2 folders) (Box 88)
    - The Skriker, 2008 Dec 4 - 6; (2 folders) (Box 88)
    - Abanthis: A Woman About Whom Nothing Is Known, 2009 Feb 26 - 28 (Box 88)
    - Metamorphoses, 2009 Apr 2 - 4 (Box 88)
    - Badass: Fighting in Never-Land, 2009 Apr 29 - May 1 (Box 88)
    - Haarlem Berlin, 2009 Oct 1 - 3 (Box 88)
    - Streetcar, 2009 Nov 11 - 14 (Box 88)
    - Rent, 2009 Dec 2 - 5; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Within the Clouds, 2010 Feb 6 (Box 89)
    - One Flea Spare, 2010 Feb 26 - 28; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Hamlet: The First Quarto, 2010 Apr 8 - 10; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Spring 2010 Shows, 2010 Spring (Box 89)
    - Homebody/Kabul, 2010 Apr 29 - May 1 (Box 89)
    - String Theory: 3 Greek Myths, 2010 Oct 7 - 8 (Box 89)
    - Miss Julie, 2010 Nov 4 - 6; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Stage Door, 2010 Nov 18 - 20; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Angels in America, 2010 Dec 2 - 4 (Box 89)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration of Vassar: Aethelred the Unready, 2011 Jan 22 - 23 (Box 89)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration of Vassar: Hallie Flanagan, 2011 Mar 1 - 3; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - MSS Award, 2011 Mar 26 (Box 89)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration of Vassar: The Cradle Will Rock, 2011 Apr 7 - 9; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Or What You Will, 2011 Apr 14 - 16 (Box 89)
    - Chic Street Man, 2011 Apr 21; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Love of the Nightingale, 2011 Apr 28 - May 1 (Box 89)
    - Rabbit Hole, 2011 Sep 29 - Oct 1 (Box 90)
    - Life is a Dream, 2011 Oct 11 - 13 (Box 90)
    - The Tempest, 2011 Oct 27 - 29; (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - Who’s Afraid of Virginia Woolf, 2011 Nov 10 - 12 (Box 90)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 2011 Dec 8 - 10 (Box 90)
    - GreenBerg, 2011 Dec 9 (Box 90)
    - Baltimore Waltz, 2012 Jan 30 (Box 90)
    - Izzy Batts, 2012 Feb 3 (Box 90)
    - Measure for Measure, 2012 Feb 28 - Mar 1 (Box 90)
    - A Long Day's Journey Into Night, 2012 Mar 29 - 31; (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - Uncle Vanya, 2012 Apr 12 - 14 (Box 90)
    - Samuel Lahne senior project, 2012 Apr 20 (Box 91)
    - Kevin Fulton senior project, 2012 Apr 27 (Box 91)
    - Baltimore Waltz, 2012 Apr 26 - 29 (Box 90)
    - Truth Values, 2012 Sep 14 (Box 90)
    - Cedars, 2012 Sep 22 (Box 90)
    - BOOM, 2012 Oct 2 - 4 (Box 90)
    - Cosmonaut, 2012 Nov 15 - 17 (Box 90)
    - Next to Normal, 2012 Oct 25 - 27 (Box 90)
    - Lysistrata, 2012 Dec 6 - 8 (Box 90)
    - Cripple of Inishmaan, 2013 Feb 14 - 16 (Box 91)
    - House of Spirits, 2013 Feb 28 - Mar 2 (Box 91)
    - Eurydice, 2013 Apr 12 - 14 (Box 91)
    - Vagina Narratives, 2013 Apr 19 - 20 (Box 91)
    - Rez Sisters, 2013 May 2 - 3 (Box 91)
    - The Little Dog Laughed, 2013 Oct 3 - 5 (Box 91)
    - Ghosts, 2013 Oct 30 - Nov 1 (Box 91)
    - The Way of the World, 2013 Nov 14 - 16 (Box 91)
    - Mouthful of Birds, 2013 Dec 5 - 7 (Box 91)
    - Beyond the Wall, 2014 Feb 3 - 4 (Box 91)
    - Hub Crawl, 2014 Feb 13 - 15 (Box 91)
    - Passion Play, 2014 Mar 27 - 29 (Box 91)
    - The Resistible Rise of Arturo Ui, 2014 Apr 17 - 19 (Box 91)
    - The Servant of Two Masters, 2014 Apr 30 - May 2 (Box 91)
    - Titus Andronicus, 2014 Apr 17 - 19; (empty) (Box 91)
    - Stockholm, 2014 Oct 2 - 4 (Box 91)
    - [M], 2014 Oct 30 - Nov1 (Box 91)
    - Here Lies the water/here stands the man, 2014 Nov 13 - 15 (Box 91)
    - Accounted for 9/11, 2014 Nov 21 (Box 91)
    - Arcadia, 2014 Dec 4 - 6 (Box 91)
    - AFTLS, 2015 Spring (Box 91)
    - God of Vengeance, 2015 Mar 5 - 7 (Box 91)
    - Cabaret, 2015 Apr 9 - 11 (Box 91)
    - Titus Andronicus, 2015 Apr 29 - May 1 (Box 91)
    - Lacunae, 2015 Oct 22 - 24 (Box 91)
    - Choephori, 2015 Nov 12 - 14 (Box 92)
    - Tildy and the Goat Head, 2015 Nov 15 (Box 92)
    - Love and Information, 2015 Dec 3 - 5 (Box 92)
    - The Mayor of Baltimore, 2016 Mar 3 - 5 (Box 92)
    - The Cherry Orchard, 2016 Apr 7 - 9 (Box 92)
    - The Anatomy of Light, MSS, 2016 Apr 24 (Box 92)
    - The Lighthouse, 2016 Apr 28 - 30 (Box 92)
    - The Hedda Gabler Project, 2016 Oct (Box 92)
    - Machinal, 2016 Oct 27 - 29 (Box 92)
    - Vieux Carre, 2016 Nov 10 - 12 (Box 92)
    - A Midsummer Nights Dream, 2016 Dec 1 - 3 (Box 92)
    - Trippin' Through Mud, 2017 Feb 16 - 18 (Box 92)
    - Fine, 2017 Mar 2 - 4; (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Huntress, 2017 Apr 6 - 8 (Box 92)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 2017 Apr 27 - 29 (Box 92)
    - MSS Play Award, 2017 (Box 92)
    - Melancholy Play, 2017 Oct 26 - 28 (Box 92)
    - Unsettled, 2017 Nov 3 (Box 92)
    - Spitfire Grill, 2017 Nov 16 - 18 (Box 92)
    - Crimes of the Heart, 2017 Nov 30 - Dec 2 (Box 92)
    - A Little Night Music, 2018 Mar 1 - 4 (Box 92)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 2018 Apr 5 - 7 (Box 92)
    - The White Moth, 2018 Apr 12 - 14 (Box 92)
    - White is Not Default, 2018 Apr 28 (Box 92)
    - Vassar on Tap, 2018 May 11 (Box 92)
    - Revolt. She Said. Revolt Again, 2018 Fall (Box 92)
    - The Effects of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon, 2018 Fall (Box 92)
    - Drums in the Night, 2018 Fall (Box 93)
    - The Flick, 2019 Oct 9 - 12 (Box 93)
    - Still, 2019 Oct 9 - 12 (Box 93)
    - O'Hysteria by Itai, 2019 Oct 31 - Nov 1 (Box 93)
    - Summertime/Wintertime, 2019 Nov 14 - 16 (Box 93)
    - Fun Home, 2019 Dec 5 - 7 (Box 93)
    - Anna Deveare Smith, 2019 May 1 - 3 (Box 93)
    - The Seagull, 2019 Apr 4 - 6 (Box 93)
    - The Northern Skies, 2019 Apr 11 - 13 (Box 93)
    - Celia Keenan-Bolger, 2020 Feb 1 - 2 (Box 93)
    - Cornelia, 2020 Feb 27 - 29 (Box 93)
    - HB Floating Palace, 2020 Apr 16 - 18 (Box 93)
    - Mississippi Mud, 2020 Apr 23 - 25 (Box 93)
    - Fefu and her Friends, 2020 Oct 23 - 25 (Box 93)
    - The Maids, 2020 Oct 20 - Nov 1 (Box 93)
    - Buried Child, 2020 Nov 13 - 15 (Box 93)
    - The Art of Refraction, 2021 Apr 24 (Box 93)
    - Jason, 2021 Apr 29 - May 1 (Box 93)
    - As you like it, 2021 May 15 - 16 (Box 93)
    - Mercury, 2021 Oct 28 - 30 (Box 93)
    - Metamorphosis, 2021 Nov 11 - 13 (Box 93)
    - Our Dear Dead Drug Lord, 2021 Dec 2 - 4 (Box 93)
    - Production files, in alphabetical order, undated; (26 folders) (Box 63)
    - Experimental Theatre - The Greek Miners, undated (Box 95)
    - Experimental Theatre - No Time for Tears by Hallie Flanagan, undated (Box 95)
    - Experimental Theatre - Pirandello, undated (Box 95)
    - Experimental Theatre - Relax! by Ethen Frank, undated (Box 95)
    - Experimental Theatre - Santos Vega, undated (Box 95)
    - Photographs - The Secret of [?] and Rosina, undated (Box 95)
    - Production files and some miscellaneous material created by Martin Fallon while he was worked as a technician and then an instructor in stage management for the Experimental Theatre, circa 1936-1944 (Box 63)
  - Stage Management Files, 2000-2021
    - Stage Management Files, in chronological order, 2000-2002 (Box 64)
    - Stage Management Files, in chronological order, 2002-2004 (Box 65)
    - Stage Management Files, in chronological order, 2004-2007 (Box 66)
    - Stage Management Files, in chronological order, 2006-2008 (Box 67)
    - The Great God Brown, 1979 Spring (Box 97)
    - The Curves Of Woman, 2001 Fall (Box 97)
    - Pygmalion, 2006 Fall (Box 97)
    - Quills, 2007 Spring (Box 97)
    - Dynamo, 2008 Spring (Box 97)
    - First Lady Suite, 2008 Fall (Box 97)
    - Three Sisters, 2008 Fall (Box 97)
    - Abanthis, 2009 Spring (Boxes 97-98)
    - Fighting From Never/Land, 2009 Spring (Box 98)
    - Hamlet: The First Quarto, 2009 Spring (Box 98)
    - Metamorphoses, 2009 Spring (Box 98)
    - Trifles, 2009 Spring (Box 98)
    - Rent, 2009 Fall (Box 98)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire, 2009 Fall (Box 98)
    - Homebody/Kabul, 2010 Spring (Box 99)
    - Within The Clouds, 2010 Spring (Box 99)
    - One Flea Spare, 2010 Fall (Box 99)
    - Angels In America, 2010 Fall (Box 99)
    - Hamlet, 2010 Fall (Box 99)
    - Stage Door, 2010 Fall (Box 99)
    - String Theory, 2010 Fall (Box 99)
    - Cradle Will Rock, 2011 Spring (Box 99)
    - The Love of the Nightingale, 2011 Spring (Box 99)
    - Life Is A Dream, 2011 Fall (Box 99)
    - Playground Hallie Flanagan Project, 2011 Fall (Box 99)
    - Rabbit Hole, 2011 Fall (Box 99)
    - The Skin Of Our Teeth, 2011 Fall (Box 100)
    - Baltimore Waltz, 2012 Spring (Box 100)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 2012 Spring (Box 100)
    - Measure For Measure, 2012 Spring (Box 100)
    - Lysistrata, 2012 Fall (Box 100)
    - Boom, 2012 Fall (Box 100)
    - Next To Normal, 2012 Fall (Box 100)
    - Cosmonauts Last Message, 2012 Fall (Box 100)
    - The Cripple Of Inishmaan, 2013 Spring (Box 100)
    - Eurydice, 2013 Spring (Box 100)
    - The House Of Spirits, 2013 Spring (Box 101)
    - The Rez Sisters, 2013 Spring (Box 101)
    - Ghosts, 2013 Fall (Box 101)
    - The Little Dog Laughed, 2013 Fall (Box 101)
    - A Mouth Full of Birds, 2013 Fall (Box 101)
    - The Way Of The World, 2013 Fall (Box 101)
    - Hub Crawl, 2014 Spring (Box 101)
    - Passion Play, 2014 Spring (Box 101)
    - The Resistible Rise Of Arturoui, 2014 Spring (Box 101)
    - Servant Of Two Masters, 2014 Spring (Box 101)
    - Arcadia, 2014 Fall (Boxes 101-102)
    - Here Lies The Water/ Here Stands The Man, 2014 Fall (Box 102)
    - [m], 2014 Fall (Box 102)
    - Stockholm, 2014 Fall (Box 102)
    - Cabaret, Vol. I-III, 2015 Spring (Box 102)
    - God Of Vengeance, 2015 Spring (Box 102)
    - Titus Andronicus, 2015 Spring (Box 102)
    - Lacunae, 2015 Fall (Box 103)
    - Love And Information, 2015 Fall (Box 103)
    - Choephori, 2015 Fall (Box 103)
    - Mercury, 2017 Oct 15 (Box 103)
    - The Seagull, 2019 Spring (Box 103)
    - The Flick, 2019 Fall (Box 103)
    - Jason, 2021 Spring (Box 103)
    - Metamorphoses, 2021 Fall (Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous Production Materials, 1924-2019
    - Avery Hall Drama - VHS tape, 2000? (Box 107)
    - CDs containing production photographs and videos, 2001-2019 (Boxes 108-109)
    - Miscellaneous Posters and Other Advertising Material, circa 1935-1991 (Folder 24.8 (Oversize))
    - Poster for The Good Woman of Setzuan [The Good Person of Szechwan], undated (Folder 24.9 (Oversize))
    - Music for Frankie and Johnny, words from "Him" by e.e. cummings, undated (Folder 24.9 (Oversize))
    - Music for Antony and Cleopatra, 1934 Dec (Box 45)
    - Music for Santos Vega, 1942 (Box 45)
    - Music for Peer Gynt, 1946 (Box 45)
    - Music for Finnegan's Wake, 1951 (Box 45)
    - Music for Greed Play, undated (Box 45)
    - Music for unidentified play, undated (Box 45)
    - Music for miscellaneous plays, undated (Box 45)
    - Negatives - Miscellaneous, undated; (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - Photographs - Miscellaneous, undated; (8 folders) (Box 95)
    - Photographs - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 106)
    - Photographs - Philaletheis production, undated (Box 95)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 1924-1960 (On shelf)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 1961-1967 (On shelf)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 1967-1972 (On shelf)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 1972-1979 (On shelf)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 1979-1985 (On shelf)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 1986-1991 (On shelf)
    - Drama Production Scrapbook, 1991-1997 (On shelf)
    - Drama Production Scrapbook, 1998-2002 (On shelf)
    - Drama Production Scrapbook, 2003-2009 (On shelf)
    - Drama Scrapbook, 2004-2008 (On shelf)
    - Drama Production Scrapbook, 2009 (On shelf)
    - Drama Production Scrapbook, 2009-2010 (On shelf)
    - Production Camera Footage - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 106)
    - VHS tapes of miscellaneous productions, 1993-2005 (Box 107)
- Series VII. Drama Major Files, 1953-1999; [RESTRICTED]
  - Drama Majors, 1953 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1954 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1956 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1957 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1958 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1959 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1960 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1961 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1962 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1963 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1964 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1965 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1966 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1967 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1968 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1969 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1970 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1971 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1972 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1973 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1974 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1975 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1976 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1977 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1978 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1979 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1980 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1981 (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1982; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1983; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Drama Majors, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1985 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1986 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1987 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1988 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1989 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1990 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1991 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1992 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1994 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1995 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1996 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1997; (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1998 (Box 105)
  - Drama Majors, 1999 (Box 105)